<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WiFi | Packet Storm</title>
    <link>/tags/wifi/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tags/wifi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>WiFi</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Packet Storm Ltd 2011 - 2021</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hue860e28d229b7c92bd38ab4efa6da1ea_865_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>WiFi</title>
      <link>/tags/wifi/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abbott Point of Care</title>
      <link>/project/abbott-point-of-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/abbott-point-of-care/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2010 - 2016: Adhoc Wifi consultancy (medical device, Abbott Wireless iStat)
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pointofcare.abbott/us/en/offerings/istat/istat-wireless&#34;&gt;https://www.pointofcare.abbott/us/en/offerings/istat/istat-wireless&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov-Dec 2015: Backported SHA-2 (sha224, sha256, sha384, sha512) support to
an old openssl library that only supported SHA-1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jan 2013 - Apr 2013: .Net app debugging and Windows 7 64-bit compatibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apr 2012 – Jun 2012:
Wifi, network protocol (TCP/IP), and, network application troubleshooting.
Visited hospitals in USA for field debugging - all issues were solved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feb 2011 – May 2011 and Sep 2010 – Nov 2010:
WiFi cryptography troubleshooting EAP-TLS, EAP-PEAP, EAP-TTLS, EAPMsCHAPv2.
Fixed bugs in wpa supplicant, fixed issues with incompatible sets of
ciphers in older windows, resolved issues regarding incompatible TLS key
exchange methods (RSA vs Diffie-Hellman key exchange).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airvana</title>
      <link>/project/airvana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/airvana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mar 2010 – Jun 2010:
Integrated Strongswan with a smartcard chip (Atmel AT98SC) which acted as an
HSM. Developed an openssl engine to integrate strongswan (IPsec daemon) with
the smartcard/HSM drivers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 2009 – Dec 2009:
IPsec hardware acceleration using iMX51 Sahara. Implemented a Linux kernel
crypto layer transform that made the Sahara crypto hardware available to the
linux kernel through the standard linux crypto APIs and thus making it available
to the IPsec module for offloading the encryption and hashing of IPsec packets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 2008 – Dec 2008: Smartcard development. PKI, RSA, X.509.
Developed drivers for the Atmel smartcard chip and provisioning tools to
provision the smartcard with X.509 credentials and secret keys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 2008 – Nov 2008: PPPoE integration: uClinux, Blackfin,
Interpeak.Speakerbus, Hoddesdon and Maidenhead&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oct 2007 – Aug 2008:
Designed, developed and tested a telephony gateway integrating RTP and T1/E1
based on a custom PowerPC board with a DSP daughtercard and running
Montavista Linux. Worked on an telephony turret device that supported SIP and
RTP calls. Wrote a CDR collection and dispatch module for the turret. Wrote a
CDR forwarding application that run on both Windows and Linux servers.
Developed multiple network python scripts for automatic testing of the devices.
Wrote scripts for manufacturing processes and testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laird Technologies</title>
      <link>/project/laird-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/laird-technologies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aug 2012 – Dec 2013: Wifi, buildroot, linux, wpa_supplicant development.
I lead the development of a new product establishing the build framework, change
and release processes, spearheading development and coaching the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jan 2010 – Feb 2010:
Implemented WiFi WPA Enterprise security (EAP, RADIUS, X.509 certificates)
for a WiFi product that only supported WPA Personal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dec 2008 – Jul 2009:
Ported TCP/IP stack to a new platform (uVelocity/ARM Cortex-M3) and
introduced SSL security and GPRS connectivity (PPP, EAP, AT commands).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;June 2006 – Oct 2007:
Integrated the Interpeak TCP/IP stack with Velosity RTOS and in-house scripting
language. Marvell Wifi 802.11 Linux driver. RS232 and power saving drivers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miura Systems</title>
      <link>/project/miura-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/miura-systems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WiFi and Bluetooth connectivity to a payment device. Integrated WiFi and
bluetooth (classic/BLE) on a Linux system using ltib build system. Implemented
the system on Realtek RTL8723. Proof of concept on Espressif ESP32.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dsiganos/vhcibridge&#34;&gt;https://github.com/dsiganos/vhcibridge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VISA VCAS qualification software
Python Flask SOAP server implementing the VISA VCAS WSDL interface and
controlling a contactless credit card payment device via bluetooth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
